justmeans2.com 2009-01-22

# Privacy Policy of JustMeans

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the JustMeans service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices

### Information Collection

_Registration:_  
In order to become a JustMeans user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your professional background (current occupation & networking objectives), and choose a password.

_Profile Information:_  
Once a user, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and networking objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the JustMeans system.   

_Information about your Contacts_ :  
In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Justmeans, you will enter their names and email addresses or will search for them by using the site. This information will be used by JustMeans to send your invitation. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.  

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into the private “My Contacts” section of our website. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.   

_Cookies & Log Files:_  
Like most web sites, JustMeans uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows JustMeans to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.  

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your JustMeans account. The next time you visit the JustMeans web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service.   

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the JustMeans web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave JustMeans. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the JustMeans service.   

_Web Beacons:_  
We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to JustMeans users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. JustMeans may “target” some ads to users that fit a certain general profile — for example, “socially responsible investors in Massachusetts.”   

To deliver these ads properly, JustMeans may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by JustMeans so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites.  

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.  

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. You will never see additional ads as a result of being a JustMeans user and JustMeans never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party.  

_Children:_  
Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

### Information Use

JustMeans is an online service dedicated to helping all types of professionals more effectively connect with each other and companies. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by JustMeans from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by JustMeans. This information can be utilized by JustMeans in such manner as JustMeans, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

_JustMeans Communications:_  
JustMeans will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of up to ten welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from JustMeans related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. JustMeans may also send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to info@justmeans.com  

_Customized Content:_  
Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network.

### Information Sharing

_Sharing Information With Third Parties:_  
JustMeans takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

JustMeans offers a “public profile” feature which allows users to publish portions of their JustMeans profile, including your “name”, but not your “email address” to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature, however JustMeans does not warrant how third-party search engines will update their cache.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. analysts, executive directors), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service. 

_Communications Between Users:_  
Many emails you initiate through JustMeans, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network). Other communications that you initiate through the JustMeans website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.  Users includes company users on the site.  If you select to become a “stakeholder” of a company, by clicking “Add to Network” or “Become a Stakeholder”, your first name, last name, email address, current company, region, and title will become viewable by that company. 

_Legal Disclaimer:_  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

### Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your JustMeans account, at any time by logging in to your account on the JustMeans website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the JustMeans website. If you close your JustMeans account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the JustMeans Privacy Policy that you have previously agree to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the JustMeans service, please send your request to [info@justmeans.com](mailto:info@justmeans.com) . Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with JustMeans under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [info@justmeans.com](mailto:info@justmeans.com) within seven business days of our receiving it.
